<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Griever's stuff</title>
    <link href="https://romhack.github.io/rss/index.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://romhack.github.io" />
    <id>https://romhack.github.io/rss/index.xml</id>
    <author>
        <name>Griever</name>
        <email>siteName@gmail.com</email>
    </author>
    <updated>2018-02-24T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <entry>
    <title>2018-02-24-</title>
    <link href="https://romhack.github.io/news/2018-02-24-.html" />
    <id>https://romhack.github.io/news/2018-02-24-.html</id>
    <published>2018-02-24T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2018-02-24T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>﻿I have finally come up with normal <a href="https://github.com/romhack/kirbyLzRle/">compression tool</a> in Haskell for NES game Kirby’s Adventure. While I still remember juicy details of struggling for compressor’s optimality and Kirby’s hacking history in general, I put some notes <a href="doc/halCompression">here</a>.</p>]]></summary>
</entry>
<entry>
    <title>2016-09-04-</title>
    <link href="https://romhack.github.io/news/2016-09-04-.html" />
    <id>https://romhack.github.io/news/2016-09-04-.html</id>
    <published>2016-09-04T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2016-09-04T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>﻿Two new documents added: a short <a href="doc/gbcHiColour">technical note</a> for GBC Hicolour technique and standard romhacking <a href="doc/snesTiles">tutorial</a> for SNES compressed graphics. The last is in Russian, as it’s too specific for Russian romhacking scene.</p>]]></summary>
</entry>
<entry>
    <title>2016-07-27-</title>
    <link href="https://romhack.github.io/news/2016-07-27-.html" />
    <id>https://romhack.github.io/news/2016-07-27-.html</id>
    <published>2016-07-27T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2016-07-27T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>﻿Some small page design updates again. Nothing special to tell about, but I’m still with the scene: as a long-delayed finish, I’ve written some compression tools for <a href="http://forum.goldensunhacking.net/index.php?topic=2624.15">‘Golden Sun’</a> (GBA) and <a href="http://chief-net.ru/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=14&amp;Itemid=39">‘Jewel Master’</a> (Genesis). Both had sophisticated compression schemes and ‘Golden Sun’, basically, was my personal long-term arch-enemy.</p>
<p>I also code some tools for smaller games in Haskell, all of them will be placed at <a href="https://github.com/romhack">my github page</a>.</p>]]></summary>
</entry>
<entry>
    <title>2015-11-07-</title>
    <link href="https://romhack.github.io/news/2015-11-07-.html" />
    <id>https://romhack.github.io/news/2015-11-07-.html</id>
    <published>2015-11-07T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2015-11-07T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://github.com/romhack/BC-BackFromSource">Battle City - Back From Source</a> was updated: fixed respawn time overflow after 42nd Level and Life bonus, taken by enemy now works correctly. Enemy counter at the right side is also updates accordingly. Thanks a lot to Max Silver for testing.</p>
<p>Small page design fix was also done.</p>]]></summary>
</entry>
<entry>
    <title>2014-06-15-</title>
    <link href="https://romhack.github.io/news/2014-06-15-.html" />
    <id>https://romhack.github.io/news/2014-06-15-.html</id>
    <published>2014-06-15T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-06-15T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Previous version of my CMS (pages were hosted at griever.magicteam.net) was written by me in PHP. Interested one can find it <a href="https://github.com/romhack/griever.magicteam-CMS">here</a>. The time has come to move to a static generated site. These pages were generated with <a href="http://jaspervdj.be/hakyll/">Hakyll</a> and have many advantages, compared to my PHP CMS:</p>
<ul>
<li>Safety. I’ve written PHP CMS as my absolutely first project in PHP. I won’t be surprised if it had multiple security vulnerabilities. God forgive me for risking my translation group’s server.</li>
<li>Speed. GitHub Pages is served with Nginx and automatically gzip’s content. No need to make minimalistic pages with poor design.</li>
<li>Markdown. All my previous design experience can be expressed with one sentence: “put everything in &lt;pre&gt;, make it look like in notepad”. Now I’m not so radical. Lists, headings and code highlight make user experience better.</li>
<li>Revision control system. Pages are just another <a href="https://github.com/romhack/romhack.github.io">Github repository</a>. Pages history can be found anytime, no backups needed.</li>
<li>Page availability time. GitHub is self-explaining.</li>
</ul>
<p>I’ve also added some Disqus and <a href="/rss/">Atom feed</a> for your convenience. Hopefully, all pages are still valid as strict XHTML. Pages are rewritten into markdown in a short time, so there still can be some errors. Please let me know, if you’ll find them.</p>]]></summary>
</entry>

</feed>
